Not it's not just react.
Deil sadece tepki deil.
There are also alternatives re-act of course is what we'll cover in this course.
Tabii ki bu ders kapsamnda ele alacamz alternatifler de var.
But there also is Engler and there would be viewed chaos and there are avarice like backbone or amber
Ancak Engler de var ve kargaa grlecektir ve omurga veya kehribar gibi agzllk
but angular and view are the most popular alternatives.
vardr ancak asal ve grnt en popler alternatiflerdir.
And I can only recommend diving into DS to to really pick your favorite.
Ve yalnzca en sevdiiniz arky semek iin DS'ye dal yapmay neririm.
I also got courses on them if you are interested.
Eer ilgileniyorsanz onlarla ilgili dersler aldm.
All three of them are great at creating highly scalable web applications that look and feel good to
de, kullancya iyi bakan ve iyi hissedecek derece leklenebilir web
the user.
uygulamalar yaratmada mkemmel.
Not so much an alternative as Jake where he you might think it is one but Shakeri is really only about
Jake'in alternatifi deil, birinin bunun olduunu dnebilecei bir yer deil, Shakeri gerekten sadece yurt iinden
traversing the dorm and targeting elements in a dorm.
gemek ve bir yurttaki eleri hedef almakla ilgilidir.
Now as you saw in our example re-act is about just declaring what you see and focusing on the logic
rneimizde grdnz gibi yeniden hareket, yalnzca grdnz beyan etmek ve manta
instead on focusing on the how and therefore react angular and view allow you to create more powerful
odaklanmak yerine manta odaklanabilmek iin nasl ve dolaysyla tepki asal ve grnm
applications because you can focus on the logic and your business model and not so much on the technical
daha gl uygulamalar oluturmanza olanak tanyorsa odaklanmaktr. i modeli ve aslnda l
side of actually reaching dead element.
elemente ulamann teknik yn deil.
You wanted to change.
Deitirmek istediniz.